hey there what's up listen I want to show you
in this video how to actually build out all
the marketing strategy for your coaching business
or online course business using AI by the end of
this video I think a lot of people don't know
how powerful AI is and so I want to demystify
some of those different things for you here's the
thing is if you can learn how to communicate with
AI the way that you would a normal human being it
can generate incredible content for you now every
single day I work with coaches and course graders
to be able to scale their businesses to be able
to make tens of millions of dollars online and I
want to help you you whether you're just getting
started you want to make maybe your first 10,000
15,000 $50,000 a month online whatever that is
I'm going to walk you through the process that
we're teaching everybody to use right now using
artificial intelligence and so there's different
stages to this you know it it a lot of people
when they're building their business they're
at different stages I'm going to show you this
and break this down from Finding Your Niche to
figuring out what the right hooks are creating
ads writing emails social media content YouTube
videos uh all those different ideas okay so let's
just come up with an idea right here and what
we're going to do is we're literally going to
create like a brand new coaching business from
scratch out of thin air and all the marketing
materials right here using Ai and I'm going to
show you my process of how I do this okay so
number one uh generate me 20 ideas very different
niches for coaching or online course businesses
okay here's 20 diverse Niche ideas for coaching
businesses let's see gut re Health reset coach
coing yoga for office workers freelance career
accelerator ethical leadership digital painting
for beginners let's do that let's do digital
painting for beginners I like that actually you
know what short story writing let's do the short
story writing Workshop okay so uh yes let's do
short story writing Workshop okay so we're going
to go with let's go with short story writing
workshop and generate let's see generate me 20 sub
niches of this category this is one of the things
I like to do when fting a niche it's coming up
with sub niches okay let's see genre specific sub
niches skill specific uh flash fiction boot camp
character Centric World building let's do a World
building right here okay let's do World building
for young adult fantasy short stories okay let's
do World building for young adult fantasy short
stories okay great um why World building matters
establishing the core elements integrating this in
there character driven World building and so the
AI is actually giving us ideas for what we could
coach and Mentor somebody on and let's say that
this is exactly like what we have an expertise in
this is great this gives us a lot of great ideas
for that can you package this into a $997 coaching
program complete with all the Community features
courses modules bonuses uh support uh print outs
Etc all right so this is where AI is so powerful
is it can help us actually come up with how we
would even package a program like this together
and you can do this same type of prompting with
your business no matter what that is deliver it
on a simple platform like kajabi your teachable
I like think ific is the one that I like to use
here's different modules that you can deliver
it on you could do a private Community slack
Discord school is a new community people are
doing uh you can provide uh coaching session
critiques principal templates this is great
and so no matter what business you're wanting
to do AI can help you come up with a lot of these
different ideas for how you're going to deliver
this to people now what I want to do is I want to
generate 20 lead magnet ideas that I could promote
on social media with paid Facebook and Instagram
ads to generate leads of potential clients okay
and this is really the step that we always
start with in our businesses is we come
up with lead magnet ideas to grow our email
list no matter what you're building you want
to have some kind of a lead magnet okay
let's see uh we could do the Young Adult
World Builder starter kit short story submission
checklist World building templates for short stor
uh let's do this let's do World building template
for short stories and a printable starter kit with
10 fantasy tropes that they might love so we're
going to kind of combine three of these together
let's make our lead magnet include the following
okay it's going to have all three of those items
in it the Young Adult World building short story
tool kit uh practical worksheet starter kit quick
sheet of different tropes and things uh tagline
for ads create fantasy worlds readers will never
forget okay uh struggling to build a believable
fantasy world in a short story get the tools you
need to bring your Young Adult World to life in
just hours fill in the blanks three starter kit so
this is amazing is it's literally able to generate
the advertisements for us even to be able to do
this and now it's going ahead and it's generating
Landing page copy your young adult fantasy awaits
let's build it together when we talk about young
adult fantasy it's like it's like Harry Potter and
things like that uh what you'll get is this let's
see visual mockups okay great um now now here's
what I would do generate for me 20 unique YouTube
video ideas very different from each other that
can be used as lead ends for this lead magnet okay
here's 20 unique YouTube video ideas five World
building mistakes that could ruin your short story
how to create a magical system that readers will
love in five 10 minutes the three-step shortcut
to building an immersive fantasy world so this
is this is awesome is these are great ideas if
you're wanting to then build up content ideas
both for what you're teaching and for YouTube
to promote let's generate 20 ideas for Instagram
reels that can go viral and eventually be used
to promote our lead magnet as the call to action
okay oh look it include these ctas if you want
ah Head Start head over to grab my free World
building kit right here skip the overwhelm my
Young Adult World building kit has everything you
need so even the AI is already thinking ahead and
coming up with that for us here are 20 Instagram
real ideas the fantasy writers struggle me trying
to figure out how my world is built POV need help
download my free kit uh it's not complicated
show the chaos of all this right there tutorials
and tips three quick quick World building tips
for Fantasy writers and so like you could even
go in and you could say you could have it um
create the info for this real in detail for me
okay and so this can help you create your
marketing materials right here is to be
able to put these different things together
oops network error occurred let's try this
again uh a hook struggling to build a believable
fantasy world show you at your desk here are three
quick tips start small think big use a notebook
uh tip number two Let the character shape the
world build it through the characters number
three use the rule of three sticking to three
features one system one Quirk one location this
is awesome super cool as far as like how it's
able to build a lot of that out for us okay so
right there you could see how we're going to then
like Market to people to be able to do something
like this write me an email that I can send to
my newsletter to promote this toolkit unlock the
secrets of building immersive fantasy worlds are
you struggling to bring your fantasy world to
life you're not alone crafting and believable
immersive World especially in short stories
can feel overwhelming you want your readers
to see Landscapes feel the culture believe the
magic where do you even start okay there we go
so right there we've been able to generate a
lot of the basics of what our marketing will
be for our Niche now what I want to do is I want
to show show you something very interesting what
I can take from this I'm going to copy all
of this and I want to say take the following
information and create one single prompt that can
generate all of this for any niche in one prompt
info so what I did was I went through and I
had it generate all this and now I'm actually
going to have the AI generate me a prompt
to create all of these different ideas in
one single prompt watch this it's a master
prompt for creating Niche specific programs
lead magnets coaching program and materials
create a complete coaching program in a
specified Niche include detailed descriptions
of the core components such as live coaching
sessions self-paced course modules this is
amazing right here right here alone you can
see that this can come up with so many
different ideas for you in your business
and let's try it out let's create a new window
with chat GPT and let's pick another Niche okay
what was one of those other niches that we
had come up with and I just want to show you
how quickly even with a master prompt like
this and by the way I'll put the prompt in
the description below this video for you we're
going to save that prompt for us so that you
can actually copy that as the master prompt and
use this in your own business this is amazing
you're going to have fun with this okay let's
take digital painting for beginners okay we're
going to create a new chat and we're going to
say Niche digital painting instructions and
then we're going to take our Master prompt
and we're going to have it generate all
the following this is an 8we coaching program
design for beginners who want to learn digital
painting live sessions Focus areas mastering
brush technique fundamentals of light Shadow
and color sketching and line art rendering
texture techniques okay self-pace modules
Community features bonuses all right 8we timeline
we're coming up with a timeline for our our
program this is awesome support materials lead
magnets digital painting starter kit tools a
free pdf essential guide uh step-by-step access
a free Workshop social media content ideas speed
painting three top three brushes every beginner
needs okay YouTube ideas how to use layers and
effectively in digital art okay so now so
here's the thing is these are great ideas
and this is the master prompt is a great place
to start with a lot of this however what I would
want to do is I would I would want to unpack
this even deeper and come up with much more
detail so this is giving us a detailed script
for one of the Instagram reels it's giving us
some marketing highlights all right now let
me take this right here and I'm going to say
generate for me sales copy for the landing page
that we will use to promote the lead magnet act
as an expert in sales copy writing and write
it in a persuasive conversational and informal
tone okay want to create studying digital art but
don't know where to start whether you're a total
beginner or just dabbling this gives you the
tools ever stare at a blank canvas overwhelmed
with all the brushes and settings you're not
alone uh we've taken the guest workout for you
the starter kit beginner friendly free Workshop
replay there you go that's awesome all right
powerful call to action different objections
what if I'm terrible at drawing guess what you
don't need to be a pro okay so now if I took
this and I could say uh generate for me a list
of the following and I actually have a document
over my website if you go to Jeremiah crow.com
free chat GPT prompts right here this document
has a number of different prompts where I show
you how to actually write the best sales copy
for landing pages so if I go through here this
is our step one step one step two okay if
I have it generate with this answer the
following questions Target customer profile
that feel overwhelmed with digital painting
and software tools frustrated by lack of hours
so if by really diving into what these these
people are struggling with you can really start
to develop better sales copy so what we did was
we worked on okay here's our offer with that
Master prompt now it's able to generate for
us what the sales copy uh pieces all look like
okay let's let's grab the Epiphany Bridge here
we're going to take this Epiphany bridge and we're
going to have it identify what's the main problem
solved what is the solution and outcome fill in
the template Fields based on this and so what
this is doing this is using various different
sales copy Frameworks to be able to write some
of the best copy to be able to promote a lead
magnet that then you could use you could use
your Instagram reels you could use your YouTube
videos to grow your email list to get people to
sign up with you and to create an irresistible
offer that gets people to become your clients okay
and so that's exactly what we do we use AI to be
able to process through and to give us ideas for
how we would communicate this with people and
that's exactly how I like to use it is I'll go
through and I'll have it I have these prompts that
I've generated I'm I'm actually going to take our
our Master prompt here um and we're going to
do this uh Master marketing ideas prompt I'm
going to put this as the very first prompt this is
really cool that we came up with this I'm actually
adding it in real time to this document because
I think it's so valuable for people there we go
there we go that's a great first prompt to use and
then start to dive into your sales copy because
it's really able to brainstorm taking one of
those Niche ideas and then it's able to brainstorm
further what to do with that and so again go grab
that prompt uh document over at my website jeremi
Kowski decom chat GPT and you'll be able to check
that out okay uh let's see clarifying the outcome
all that it's fine-tuning this language they
don't just want tutorials they want a clear guided
path okay great see what is the ultimate end
outcome that somebody gets and so what we're
doing is we're having the AI generate for us bold
promises we're having it come up with well-crafted
headlines and ideas that really highlight what
the outcome is that we're delivering to people
that's what these prompts are designed to do
they're designed to pull out of the idea one
single idea for what the niche is to come up
with some of these very great ideas for this
okay ultimate outcome of somebody who
wants to work with a coach for the
offer is generating the outcome because
we want it to be outcom driven overall
in our marketing if we attach it to the
desired outcome the desired transformation
it really will dial in much better
that's what step number five is right
here
okay step a step B okay and then step six is
our storytelling sales copy framework where
what it does is it generates for us even better
sales copy right here and what I like to do is I
have it right at first and then then rewrite it
in the tone of Sandy Kowski you might notice my
name is Jeremiah Kowski Sandy Kowski is my mom's
name we actually built a coaching business over
at the site AAL change.com and we're we were
able to actually scale this business to over
$20 million a year and a lot of the sales
copy was actually written in the style that
the AI knows how to mirror uh because we've been
doing it for so long okay so that's why I have it
rewrited in the tone of Sandy Kowski and this
is our final kind of sales copy language that
wanted to do are you tired of feeling overwhelmed
every time you try to create digital art have you
ever stared at your screen completely lost not
sure where to start your brush Strokes don't
even to look right your layers are a mess before
you know it that excitement creates frustration I
know what it's like I've been there too when
I first got started doing this I spent hours
on YouTube trying to figure it out thinking
I'll never be able to do this but here's the
thing the problem wasn't me it was a lack of
clear step-by-step guidance and so what this
is doing is this allows us to actually create
a lead magnet that can be written with that
and then here's the Sandy Kowski tone one listen
friend if you've been struggling with this let
me tell you something it's not your fault you
got the patch and you got the drive every time
you try to do it it feels like you're drowning I
get it I've been there I've had the T-shirt when
I first started I thought I'll just watch a few
tutorials and I'll be creating a masterpiece in
no time instead I wasted hours trying to figure
out how to use the brushes how to fix my messy
layers and why my art just didn't look right
every time I tried I end up thinking maybe I'm
just not cut out for this sound familiar here's
the truth you don't need fancy tools or natural
talent to become a digital artist you just
need somebody to show you a clear way so again
you can promote this with different uh offers
with different idea and let me take this right
here and I'm going to modify this just a
little bit the second half of this master
prompt and I'm going to say generate I'm going
to say generate new ideas based on the above
for lead magnets with its components okay lead
magnet number one Ultimate Painting tool kit
mini tutorial video number two 5-day digital
Kickstart challenge bite size challenge uh uh
complete simple sketches to build confidence
number three the beginners guide to digital
art techniques detailed explanation of basic
techniques like blending shading layering all
right uh lead in social media content before
and after my first digital art versus now three
must have tools for beginners how to avoid
the number one beginner mistake in making
digital art uh three myths about digital art
that you need to stop believing a day in the
life of a beginner digital artist digital art for
beginners top mistakes beginners make procreate
versus Photoshop versus CR which one is best
for beginners layer management 101 so again
gives us lots of ideas for YouTube videos gives us
ideas for Instagram reels lead magnets even email
marketing that we we can use to promote this and
so whether you're just getting started building
your coaching business or you're trying to get
off the ground AI is an invaluable tool as I've
shown you to brainstorm and come up with ideas
that you can then take those ideas and use them
to turn into other ideas and what I like to do
is my little ideas come up with idea babies they
birth new ideas and then that new idea turns into
something else and then it turns into something
else and it turns into something else and that
eventually is what becomes our best marketing
and so listen if you're like I don't know how to
come up with my business I don't know how how to
come up with ideas I don't know how to Market it
I've just shown you in less than 20 minutes two
different niches two different entirely different
business models AI is brilliant at doing this so
i' highly recommend get a chat GPT account use
chat GPT 40 it's incredible at what it does and
I think you'll be able to put all this together
as well now here's the other thing too is in my
coaching program the client growth accelerator I
work with people every single week on how do we
take their offers how do we piece it all together
and then how do we actually make sure that they
get sales because all these different marketing
things are great but without sales it's not worth
anything and so again what I'd love to do is I'd
love to invite you to jump into my client growth
accelerator you can check out there's actually a
training that I have below here where you can walk
through how to get 10 to 20 brand new clients
every single month in your business how to
generate $100,000 a month in a coaching business
and there's an opportunity for you to jump into
our accelerator program when you check that out
Below in the description below I think you'll
find it extremely valuable for you I'll talk soon
I'll see you in the next video have a good one